techpreparation.com 2009-04-16

# Privacy Policy

TechPreparation.com , is committed to protecting your privacy and provide technology that gives you a secure online experience. The majority of the website can be viewed without giving us any information about yourself. However for certain areas of the website and for certain functions you are required to enter personal information. This privacy statement explains the data we collect and its use in these situations.

TechPreparation.com protects the security of your personal information and honors your choice for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

TechPreparation.com has taken adequate steps and measures to protect personal information from being misused. 

While providing your personal information, you acknowledge that no website security procedures are completely foolproof and you agree that you are submitting your personal information to TechPreparation.com website at your own risk. 

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. Generally but not limited to, this information is requested when you sign up to become a member of  TechPreparation.com and when you send us feedback.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password to TechPreparation.com, so do not share these with others. 

To enable us to monitor and improve the site, we may gather certain information about you when you use the website, including details of your Operating system: e.g., Windows, DOS, Macintosh, or UNIX; Browser version and type: e.g., Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer; Browser language: e.g., Java or Unix; Internet Service Provider (ISP): e.g., Mind Spring or AOL.  Tracking Script : e.g., Google Analytics.

????

 IP address: a unique number assigned to every computer on the Internet. The type of information that TechPreparation.com can infer from the IP address is a geographic location. Your domain: e.g., .COM, net, or .edu. This is standard information that is available with all communication sent on the Internet. 

Adequate facility has been provided to unsubscribe from mailing list at any point of time, if you are not able to unsubscribe from mailing list please send us an email or use "Contact Us" form and inform us regarding the same.

**Personally Identifiable Information Collected**

Personal information collected from TechPreparation.com often is limited to name, email address, location, IP Number but may from time to time include other information when needed to provide a service that you requested. We store these information in our database and use your personal information to contact you when you have a query and to supply you with a newsletter / support / registration procedure etc., if you request one. 

**Cookies and Clickstream**

We may use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters sent to your computer) only to identify your browser and to store information such as your User ID and your session identifiers to enable us to identify whether you are registered on to the site and, if so, to shortcut your access to the site and for user preferences. We will only read cookies from your cookie file placed there through your web browser's interaction with the site. 

We may also use cookies to help us determine how long users view particular content, which particular content (e.g. advertising) users view, which content or sites users link to, and which TechPreparation.com services visitors use.

Though browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. 

If cookies are refused or disabled, some of our website’s features and services may not function properly.

**RSS Feeds**

If you subscribe to our RSS feed with your email address, your email address will be saved at feedburner.com, feedblitz.com or any feed provider used and TechPreparation.com will have access to such email address. email addresses will be used ONLY for sending the RSS feed from our web site. email addresses will never be sold, disclosed or rented to any third party. 

**Ad Servers**

TechPreparation.com has relationships with different companies like Google Adsense,  Clicksor etc., and or any other companies not specifically mentioned herein who place ads on TechPreparation.com pages. Whenever you visit TechPreparation.com or any of it pages, ad server companies, may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information with the help of cookies. If you need more information regarding google adsense, please go through Google privacy policy at [ http://www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

**Third Party Website / Other sites**

We occasionally use third party companies to provide services on our behalf. We will only provide those companies the information they require to deliver their service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

You may also be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use affiliate services, third-party content, or third-party software. 

**Protection for Personally Identifiable Information Collected**

We endeavor to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal Data including the use of encryption technology, but TechPreparation.com cannot guarantee the security of any data that you disclose online. 

**User information**

When you register in our website, You will be asked to provide TechPreparation.com with certain information including, without limitation, a valid email address (your "Information"). In addition to the terms and conditions that may be set forth in any privacy policy on this website, You understand and agree that TechPreparation.com may disclose to third parties, on an anonymous basis, certain aggregate information contained in your registration application. TechPreparation.com will not disclose to any third party your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number without your prior consent, except to the extent necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws or in legal proceedings where such information is relevant. TechPreparation.com reserves the right to offer third party services and products to You based on the preferences that You identify in your registration and at any time thereafter; such offers may be made by TechPreparation.com or by third parties. 

TechPreparation.com does not independently verify the information provided by candidates or the identity of candidates or employers. 

TechPreparation.com does not intend to collect any information directly from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may use TechPreparation.com website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. In the event that TechPreparation.com learns that it has inadvertently collected information from a child under the age of 13, any and all such information will be promptly deleted from TechPreparation.com systems.

**Access, update or delete your information**

Once your register at TechPreparation.com, you are responsible for maintaining and updating, as applicable, your account Registration Data with current, accurate and complete information. You may view, update and/or edit the Registration Data you have provided to TechPreparation.com by logging in to your account and following the appropriate instructions. 

**Feedback, Support Mails and Member communication**

Whenever you send any feedback and or email or any other communication to admin/support or use the "Contact Us" form, TechPreparation.com may retain such communications/emails in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and to improve our services. 

**Links**

Our site may link to other web sites. This Internet Privacy Policy does not apply to such links or third party websites and we are not responsible for their data policies or procedures or their content. 

**Changes to this policy**

TechPreparation.com may revise these Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page periodically to review the Terms and Conditions and the Privacy Policy, because they are binding on you. The terms "You" and "User" as used herein refer to all individuals and/or entities accessing this web site for any reason.

Check Aptitude Interview Questions for more Aptitude Questions

Check Placement Papers for more IT Companies Paper
